Guide to the Time Inc. Fortune Publishing and Business Records 1929-2005 MS 3009-RG 25
New-York Historical Society
- Series II. Public Relations Department Files, 1987-1991; 6.85 Linear feet in 7 record cartons
  - Subseries II.A. Public Relations Director Emma Dockendorff, 1989-1991; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    - Wall Street Journal Ads, 1990 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 10)
    - World Affairs Council, 1990-1990 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 11)
    - Worldwide Corporate Communications Seminar, 1991 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 12)
  - Subseries II.B. Public Relations Office Files, 1987-1991; 1.1 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    The Public Relations Office Files focus on events that the Public Relations department helped arrange as well as material collected by the department documenting the public's perception of Fortune. Staff represented include Francine Uomoleale, Gary Belis, and Emma Dockendorff. Records include job descriptions, invoices, press and radio reports, press kits, photographs, negatives, and clippings.
    Arranged alphabetically.
    - AFIPS: Product Awards Ceremony, 1987 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 13)
    - Fortune: 60th Anniversary, 1990, undated (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 14-16)
    - Fortune: 60th Anniversary: Pierre, undated (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 17-18)
    - Fortune: 60th Anniversary: Rainbow Room, undated (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 19-20)
    - Fortune: 60th Anniversary: Spain, undated (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 21)
    - Fortune: Atlanta Event, 1987 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 22)
    - Fortune: Covers, undated (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 23)
    - Fortune: Covers: First Fortune 500 Cover, undated (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 24)
    - Invoices, 1990 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 25-29)
    - Invoices [RESTRICTED], 1990 (Offsite-box R42)
    - Press Pickup Totals, 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 2905, Folder 30-33)
    - Press Pickup Totals, 1990 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 1)
    - Public Relations Assistant Job Description, 1991 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 2)
    - Radio Clearance and Exceptions Reports, 1989 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 3)
    - Radio Scripts, 1991 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 4)
    - Rate Base: 1990 Nov. 15 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 5-6)
    - Weeden, Finkle and Fay Invitations, 1987 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 7)
  - Subseries II.C. Press Releases, 1989-1990; 2.25 Linear feet in 3 record cartons
    Press Releases were collected by the Public Relations department between 1989 and 1990. These press releases announced special issues of Fortune or articles that were soon to be published. The dates on files indicate the date of an issue's or article's publication rather than when a press release was distributed.
    Organized in reverse chronological order.
    - 1990 December, 1990 November 14 - December 13 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 8-13)
    - 1990 November, 1990 October 17 - November 8 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 14-17)
    - 1990 October, 1990 October 3-28 (Offsite-box 2906, Folder 18-22)
    - 1990 October, 1990 September 19 - October 10 (Offsite-box 2907, Folder 1-3)
    - 1990 September, 1990 August 21 - September 19 (Offsite-box 2907, Folder 4-10)
    - 1990 July, 1990 June 13 - July 24 (Offsite-box 2907, Folder 11-15)
    - 1990 June, 1990 May 16-31 (Offsite-box 2907, Folder 16-17)
    - 1990 May, 1990 April 17 - May 11 (Offsite-box 2907, Folder 18-19)
    - 1990 April, 1990 April 3-4 (Offsite-box 2907, Folder 20-21)
    - 1990 April, 1990 March 20 - April 4 (Offsite-box 2908, Folder 1-2)
    - 1990 March, 1990 August 8, 1990 February 20 - March 6, undated (Offsite-box 2908, Folder 3-9)
    - 1990 January, 1990 January 9, 1990 December 14 (Offsite-box 2908, Folder 12-13)
    - 1989 April, 1989 April 25 (Offsite-box 2908, Folder 14-15)
  - Subseries II.D. Television and Radio Transcript Files, 1990-1991; 1 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    The Radio and Television Transcript files cover the period of 1990 to 1991 and include transcripts from Fortune editors' appearances on radio and television programs. The specific shows included in this subseries are Inside Business and Your Dollar. Additionally, there are transcripts from editor appearances on the Financial News Network.
    - Financial News Network, 1990-1991, undated (Offsite-box 2908, Folder 16-17)
    - Inside Business, 1990 (Offsite-box 2908, Folder 18-20)
    - Inside Business, 1990 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 1-4)
    - Your Dollar, 1990 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 5-8)
  - Subseries II.E. Newspaper, Radio, and Television Clippings Files, 1989-1991; 1.5 Linear feet in 2 record cartons
    The Newspaper, Radio, and Television Clippings Files cover the period of 1989 to 1991 and includes collected newspaper clippings as wells as transcripts of radio and television shows that mention specific issues of Fortune or featured articles. The folder titles appear to relate to specific issues of Fortune rather than the dates of the clippings. of a specific clipping was published.
    Arranged in original order.
    - 1991 February 12, 1990 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 9)
    - 1991 June 4, 1990, undated (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 10)
    - 1990 December 3-31, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 11-13)
    - 1990 November 5-19, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 14-21)
    - 1990 October 8-22 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 22-23)
    - 1990 September 10-24 (Offsite-box 2909, Folder 24-25)
    - 1990 August 13-27, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 1-2)
    - 1990 July 2-30, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 3-5)
    - 1990 June 18 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 6)
    - 1990 May 21 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 7)
    - 1990 April 9-23, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 8-17)
    - 1990 March 12-26 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 18-19)
    - 1990 February 26 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 20)
    - 1990 January 1-29, 1989-1990 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 21-23)
    - Investor's Guide: Fall 1990, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 24)
    - Pac Rim: Fall 1990 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 25)
    - Spring 1990 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 26)
    - Spring 1990: Saving Our Schools, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 2910, Folder 27-29)
- Series III. Advertising Sales Department Records, 1930-1974; 0.25 Linear feet on 6 reels of microfilm
  The Advertising Sales Deparment Records contains the Fortune Advertiser Record Cards which are are on microfilm. The dates refer to the original material and not the creation of the microfilm. Each record card contains the magazine issue date for the advertisement, size of ad, if it is in black-and-white or color, and the cost.
  Organized alphabetically by name of company or organization placing ad, not the name of the product.
  - Advertiser Record Cards, 1930-1974 (Offsite-box 3326)
- Series IV. Fortune Data Bank Publications Fulfillment Files, 1983; 0.5 Linear feet in 1 document case
  Fortune Data Bank Publications Fulfillment Files contains a sampling of requests from readers to purchase other publications by Fortune advertised in the magazine. These include editorial studies, market surveys, directories, and conference reports designed to "give you an edge in expertise, get you more for your management money." Publications include "Business and Banking", "Crosscurrents", "DDP Decisions", "Double 500 Directory", "Why Corporate America Moves Where", "Working Smarter", and "World Business Directory".
  Organized alphabetically based on the original arrangement.
  - General, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 1-2)
  - General: International, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 3-5)
  - General: United States and Canada, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 6)
  - Business and Banking, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 7-9)
  - DDP Decisions, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 10-12)
  - Facility Location Decisions, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 13-16)
  - Crosscurrents, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 17)
  - Working Smarter, 1983 (Offsite-box 4179, Folder 18)
- Series V. Audiovisual [RESTRICTED], 1978-2005; 32 Linear feet in 32 record cartons
  The Audiovisual series covers the period of 1978 to 2005 and contains audiovisual materials that were collected by promotions, publicity, public affairs, and public relations staff. The majority of materials document Fortune editors' appearances on television as well as events hosted by the magazine. All subseries are based on the original arrangement of the materials.
  This series contains six subseries:
  Subseries V.A. Fortune Editors on TV
  Subseries V.B. Fortune Satellite Press Tours
  Subseries V.C. Fortune Week
  Subseries V.D. Wall Street Week with Fortune
  Subseries V.E. Miscellaneous
  Subseries V.F. Box Labels
  - Subseries V.A. Fortune Editors on TV, 1992-2001; 15.25 Linear feet in 16 record cartons
    The Fortune Editors on TV subseries covers the period of 1992 to 2001. Contained within this subseries are videotaoes which document Fortune editor and writer appearances on television shows. Additionally, there is one audiocassette with the audio of an editor appearance on a television show.
    Arranged chronologically.
    - Fortune Magazine: Eyewitness News: KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco, 1992 January 23 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (18 secs): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Fortune Magazine' Eyewitness News KPIX-TV (CBS) San Francisco January 23, 1992 6:00 am :18". On label on case side: "January 23, 1992 Eyewitness News KPIX-CBS San Francisco".
    - Jim Rogers/Fortune Magazine: Channel 6 News Weekend: WBRC-TV (NBC) Birmingham, 1992 March 1 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min., 17 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Jim Rogers/Fortune Magazine' Channel 6 News Weekend WBRC-TV (NBC) Birmingham March 1, 1992 5:30-6:00pm 2:17". On label on case side: "Jim Rogers/Fortune Channel 5 News, WBRC, Birmingham 3-1-92"
    - Marshall Loeb: Nightline: ABC-TV Network, 1992 April 17 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (7 min. 10 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Marshall Loeb' Nightline ABC-TV Network April 17, 1992 11:30-12:30 AM ET 7:10". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb on Nightline 4-17-92".
    - Segment with Alex Taylor of Fortune Magazine: The 10 O'Clock News, 1992 April 21 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 10 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Segment with Alex Taylor of Fortune Magazine' The 10 O'Clock News 4/21/92, WNYW, 10 p.m., (2:10)". On label on case side: "Editor Interviews Fox News-A.Taylor 4-92 Fortune"
    - Geoffry Colvin, Fortune Magazine: CBS This Morning: CBS-TV Network, 1992 April 23 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (5 min., 26 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Geoffry Colvin, Fortune Magzine' CBS This Morning CBS-TV Network April 23, 1992 7:00-9:00 AM ET 5:26". On label on case side: "Editors' Interviews G.Colin-CBS This Morning 4-92".
    - Segment on the auto industry with Alex Taylor of Fortune Magazine: The 10 O'Clock News, 1992 May 8 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (3 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Segment on the auto industry with Alex Taylor of Fortune Magazine' The 10 O'Clock News 5/18/92, WNYW, 10 p.m., (3:00)". On label on case side: "Fortune WNYW Fox, 5/18/92, Alex Taylor Editor's Interviews".
    - Vivian Brownstein, Economist-Fortune Magazine: The 10 O'Clock News: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1992 July 2 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min., 20 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Vivian Brownstein, Economist-Fortune Magazine' The Ten O'Clock News WNYW-TV (Fox) New York July 2, 1992 10:00-11:00 PM 2:20". On label on case side: "Fortune WNYW Fox Business News--7/2/92 Vivian Brownstein Editor's Interviews".
    - Alison Sprout: Products to Watch, 1992 September 3 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min., 5 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "-Pructs to Watch -Talent: Sprout -9/3/92 -R/T: 2:05". On label on case side: "Alison Sprout Products to Watch 9-3-92 Fortune Editor's Interviews".
    - Ann Morrison: Good Morning America: ABC Network, 1992 September 7 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (7 min., 30 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "Good Morning America Interview with Morrison ABC Network 9-7-92 8am Length 7 1/2 minutes". On label on case side: " GMA/Ann Morrison/9-7-92 Fortune Editor's Interviews".
    - Marshall Loeb: World Today: CNN Cable, 1992 September 17 (Offsite-box 2911, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (5 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "World Today Marshall Loebs CNN Cable 9-17-92 6pm Length 5 minutes". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb on CNN -- Economic Currency Crisis 9-17-92 5:00".
    - Marshall Loeb: World Today: CNN Cable, 1992 September 17 (Offsite-box 2911, Folder 1)
      Previously in case with World Today: Marshall Loeb: CNN Cable, Box 2911 Item 10.
    - Products to Watch with Alison Sprout of Fortune, 1992 September, 1993 July-August (Offsite-box 2911, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic): On label on case front: "Products to Watch Aired on NY #1 Reporter Alison Sprout of Fortune Magazine 1. Sept. 1992 2. July 1993 3. Aug. 1993". On label on case side: "Sept 1992 July 1993 Aug. 1993 Products to Watch With Alison Sprout of Fortune". On label on cassette: "Products to Watch Fortune Magazine Segment Aired on NY #1 Reporter: Alison Sprout 1. Sept. 1992 2. July 1993 3. Aug. 1993 Production: A.Villet MPI/TVPD Products to Watch with Alison Sprout of Fortune".
    - Alex Taylor: Business Insiders: CNBC, 1992 October 19 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (7 min., 35 sec.): On label on cassette front: "'Segment with Alex Taylor of Fortune Magazine' Business Insiders 10/29/92, CNBC, 6 p.m., (7:35)". On label on cassette side: "Business Insiders -- Alex Taylor 10/29/92, CNBC Fortune".
    - Ann Morrison: Beyond the Glass Ceiling: World Today: CNN, 1992 November 16 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 2)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (9 min., 5 sec.): On label on cassette front: "'Beyond the Glass Ceiling' The World Today 11/16/92, CNN, 6 p.m., (9:05) Ann Morrison". On label on cassette side: "Ann Morrison Fortune CNN-11/16/92 "Beyond the Glass Ceiling".
    - Ann Morrison: Breaking Glass Ceiling: Sonya Live: CNN, 1992 November 18 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (14 sec.): On label on case front: "Anne Morrison Breaking Glass Ceiling Sonya Live CNN (Cable) November 18, 1992 1:00 PM 00:14 Master". On label on case side: "Anne Morrison Breaking Glass Ceiling November 18, 1992 Fortune Ed's Intvs". On label on cassette: "Anne Morrison Breaking Glass Ceiling November 18, 1992".
    - James Robinson/Fortune Magazine Release and Nightly Business Report, 1992 December 7 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (U-Matic) (2 min., 30 sec.): On label on case front: "James Robinson/Fortune Magazine Release Moneyline - CNN (Cable) Dec. 7, 1992 7:00PM 2:00 Nightly Business Report - WNET-TV (PBS) NY Dec 7, 1992 6:30PM 00:30". On label on case side and cassette: "James Robinson/Fortune Magazine Release Dec. 7, 1992".
    - Marshall Loeb: Viewer Call-In Program, 1992 December 14 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on cassette side: "Marshall Loeb Viewer Call-In Program 12/14/92". On label on cassette front: "Title Viewer Call-In Program Recorded Monday, December 14, 1992".
    - Marshall Loeb on NY 1, 1992 December 16 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on cassette front: "Marshall Loeb on NY 1 - NAFTA 12/16/92". On label on cassette side: "Marshall Loeb NY 1 News 12-16-92 NAFTA".
    - Year End Interview with Marshall Loeb, 1993 January 12 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (4 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "Year End Interview with Marshall Loeb Managing Editor Fortune Magazine 1/12/93 Running Time: 4 minutes". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb Year-End Int. 1-12-93".
    - Marshall Loeb: Fortune's Most Admired Corporations and Sears: NY1, 1993 January 28 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Marshall Loeb Fortune's Most Admired Corporations and Sears NY1 1/28/93". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb - NY1 Most Admired Corps. 1-28-93". On label on cassette: "Marshall Loeb Fortune's Most Admired Corporations Sears 1/28/93".
    - Marshall Loeb/Fortune Magazine: ABC World News Sunday: ABC-TV Network, 1993 January 31 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Marshall Loeb/Fortune Magazine' ABC World News Sunday ABC-TV Network January 31, 1993 6:30-7:00 PM ET 2:00". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb/Fortune ABC World News Tonight 1/31/93, 6:30-7:00 PM 2:00".
    - Marshall Loeb/Fortune Magazine: ABC World News Sunday: ABC-TV Network, 1993 January 31 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (2 min.):On label on case front: "Marshall Loeb/Fortune Magazine ABC World News Sunday ABC-TV Network 1/31/93, 6:30-7:00 PM 2:00". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb/Fortune ABC World News Tonight 1/31/93, 6:30-7:00 PM 2:00".
    - Bill Saporito, Fortune/Management at American Express: Business Insiders: CNBC, 1993 February 1 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (6 min., 4 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Bill Saporito, Fortune/Management at American Express' Business Insiders C N B C February 1, 1993 6:00-6:30 PM ET 6:04". On label on case side: "CNBC, Bill Saporito, On American Express 2/1/93".
    - Stratford Sherman of Fortune Magazine: Mac Newill/Lehrer Newshour: WNET TV (PBS) NY, 1993 February 3 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (25 min.): On label on case front: "Stratford Sherman of Fortune Magazine Mac Newill/Lehrer Newshour WNET TV (PBS)NY February 3, 1993 7:00PM 25:00". On label on case side and cassette: "Stratford Sherman of Fortune Magazine February 3, 1993".
    - Marshall Loeb, M. Forbes Jr., S. Shepard: Nightly Business Report, 1993 February 15 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on cassette side: "2/15/93--Nightly Busi. Report M. Loeb, M. Forbes, Jr., S. Shepard". On label on cassette front: "Broadcast Date: 2.15.93 Subject: Pres. Day".
    - Anne Morrison, Fortune Magazine: Donahue: WNBC-TV (NBC) New York, 1993 February 24 (Offsite-box 2912, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (57 min., 16 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Ann Morrison, Fortune Magazine' Donahue (Syndicated) WNBC-TV (NBC) New York February 24, 1993 4:00-5:00 PM 57:16". On label on case side: "Donahue Ann Morrison 2/24/93".
    - Marshall Loeb, Fortune Magazine: The World Today: CNN, 1993 April 15 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 1)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (11 min., 15 sec.): On label on case front: "'Marshall Loeb, Fortune Magazine' The World Today April 15, 1993 6:00-7:00 PM ET 11:15". On label on case side: "Marshall Loeb - CNN - 4/15/93 The World Today - VAT". On label on cassette: "Marshall Loeb, Fortune Magazine" The World Today CNN April 15, 1993 6:00-7:00 PM ET 11:15".
    - Nancy Perry: Glass Ceiling: Good Morning America, 1993 April 16 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 2)
      1 video cassette (VHS): On labels on case front and cassette: "Good Morning America Nancy Perry--Glass Ceiling 4/16/93 dupe". On label on case side: "DUPE GMA--4/16/93 Nancy Perry/Glass Ceiling".
    - Nancy Perry: Glass Ceiling: Good Morning America, 1993 April 16 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 3)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Good Morning America-4/16/93 Nancy Perry--Glass Ceiling 8:00 a.m. original". On label on case side: "Good Morning America -- 4/16/93 Nancy Perry Discusses the Glass Ceiling". On label on cassette: "Good Morning America - 4/16/93 Nancy Perry -- Glass Ceiling 8:00 a.m.".
    - Nancy Perry: The Glass Ceiling: Good Morning America, 1993 April 16 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 4)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Good Morning America 4/16/93 - Nancy Perry The Glass Ceiling Dupe". On label on case side: "GMA--4/16/93: N. Perry Discusses The Glass Ceiling DUPE". On label on cassette: "Good Morning America 4/16/93 0 Nancy Perry The Glass Ceiling".
    - Ann Reilly: NY1 News, 1993 April 16 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 5)
      1 videocassette (VHS): 1/2 in. On label: "NY1 News - Ann Reilly DOWS 4-16-93 VAT".
    - Stratford Sherman, Fortune Magazine: Business Insiders: CNBC, 1993 April 26 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 6)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (8 min., 1 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Stratford Sherman, Fortune Magazine' Business Insiders C N B C April 26, 1993 6:00-6:30 PM ET 8:01". On label on case side: "Stra Sherman-CNBC 4-26-93-Clinton's 100 Days".
    - Allan Demaree on the Fortune SVC 500: O'Clock News: WNYW-TV, 1993 May 12 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 7)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (1 min., 4 sec.): On label on case front: "WNYW-TV O'Clock News Allan Demaree on the Fortune SVc 500 5/12/93 1:04". On label on case side: "WNYW-Allan Demaree-Fortune Svc 500 5/12/93".
    - Allan Demaree/Fortune Magazine: 10 O'Clock News: WNYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1993 May 12 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 8)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (1 min., 4 sec.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Allan Demaree/Fortune Magazine' 10 O'Clock News WNYW-TV (Fox) New York May 12, 1993 10:00-11:00 PM 1:04". On label on case side: "Allan Demaree - Fox News '93 Fortune SVC 500 5-12-93"
    - Strat Sherman: The Charlie Rose Show, 1993 June 21 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 9)
      1 videocassette (VHS) (30 min.): On label on side of cassette: "The Charlie Rose Show -- 6/21/93 30:00 Sculley resignation; information superhighways; -Strat Sherman-". One label on front of cassette: "Phar Lap 1:47".
    - Strat Sherman: The Charlie Rose Show, Business Insiders (CNBC), and McNeil Lehrer (CNBC), 1993 June 18-21, Undated (Offsite-box 2913, Item 10)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "Strat Sherman 1) The Charlie Rose Show, 6/21 Electronic superhighways 2)Business Insiders, CNBC, 6/18 3) McNeil Lehrer and CNBC". On label on case side: "S. Sherman-CH. Rose 6-21-93".
    - Ann Reilly Down, Fortune Magazine: 10 O'Clock News: WUYW-TV (Fox) New York, 1993 June 25 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 11)
      1 videocassette (U-matic) (2 min.): On labels on case front and cassette: "'Ann Reilly Down, Fortune Magazine' 10 O'Clock News WUYW-TV (Fox) New York June 25, 1993 10:00-11:00 PM 2:00". On label on case side: "Ann Reilly Dowd 25 S. Sherman 6/93 CNBC".
    - Ann Reilly Dowd: How Budget Will Affect Consumers: CNN, 1993 August 4 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 12)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "CNN, 8/4/93, Ann Reilly Dowd How Budget Will Affect Consumer". On label on case side: "CNN 8-4-93 Ann Reilly Dowd Fortune How Budget Will Affect Consumers".
    - Ann Reilly Dowd: How Budget Will Affect Consumers: CNN, 1993 August 4 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 13)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label on case front: "CNN, 8/4/93, Ann Reilly Dowd How Budget Will Affect Consumers". On label on case side: "Cnn, 8/4/93, Ann Reilly Dowd Fortune How Budget Will Affect Consumers".
    - Marshall Loeb: Viewers Call-In About Budget: CNN, 1993 August 6 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 14)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On label: "CNN 8/6/93-M. Loeb-Original- Viewers Call-In About Budget".
    - Marshall Loeb: Viewers Call in About Budget: CNN, 1993 August 6 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 15)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case front and side: "CNN, 8/6/93, Marshall Loeb Viewers Call in About Budget".
    - Marshall Loeb: Viewers Call in about Budget: CNN, 1993 August 6 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 16)
      1 videocassette (VHS): On labels on case front and side: "CNN, 8/6/93, Marshall Loeb Viewers Call in about Budget".
    - Rob Norton: Prime News Saturday: CNN, 1993 August 7 (Offsite-box 2913, Item 17)